(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
みんなこんねねー！
Hello everyone, Kon-nene!
ツルツルツルツルツルツラ...
Tsuru-tsuru-tsuru-tsuru-tsura...
パー！
Pa!
ホロライブ5期生、オレンジ担当、アイドルVTuberの桃鈴ねねです！
Hololive 5th gen orange representative, idol VTuber Momosuzu Nene here!
今日はねぽらぼアイドル衣装のお披露目に来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to the reveal of our Nepolabo idol costumes today!
イエーイ！みんなコメントありがとう！
Yay! Thank you for all the comments, everyone!
今日のハッシュタグは #ねぽらぼアイドル衣装 でツイートして、いっぱいね、感想の嵐に、追いやっちゃってください！
Please tweet with today's hashtag #NepolaboIdolCostume, and flood us with a storm of your impressions!
よろしくお願いします！
I'm counting on you!
さぁ、ねねは5期生でトップバッターを務めさせていただきます。
Now, Nene will be the first one up among the 5th generation.
あとに続くみんなのためにも、ここで大盛り上がりしていきましょう！
Let's get fired up here for the sake of everyone following after!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you very much!
というわけで、1曲目聴いてください。
So, please listen to the first song.
1曲目じゃないや、1曲聴いてください。
Wait, not the first song. Please listen to a song.
最高速 Fall in Love
Saikosoku Fall in Love
モンスター モンスター
Monster monster
モンモンモンモン モンスター
Mon-mon-mon-mon monster
モンスター モンスター
Monster monster
モンモンモンモン モンスターズライフ
Mon-mon-mon-mon monsters' life
人目ばっかり気にしてないで
Don't just worry about what others think,
大胆に かつ慎重に ターゲットを決めるの
Boldly yet carefully, decide on your target.
挨拶はほどほどに ココロの準備が済んだら
Keep greetings brief, and once your heart is ready,
いざ尋常に
Let's do this fair and square!
見つけた隙は即座に狙い定め
Aim immediately for any opening you find and...
撃つ！ 撃つ！ 撃つ！ 撃つ！ よし！
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot! Shoot! Alright!
遠慮は必要ない
No need for hesitation,
あとは確実にハートを射止めるだけで
now just surely win their heart.
愛だったら ほんのちょっとでいい
If it's love, just a little bit is enough.
それより 何より 欲望のおもむくまま さぁ
More than that, more than anything, just follow your desires!
ねぇ ダーリン 君がいるから最強じゃない？
Hey darling, aren't we the strongest 'cause you're here?
ずっと一緒なら最高じゃない？
If we're always together, isn't it the best?
この先 何があったって 君とならオールOK
No matter what happens ahead, if I'm with you, it's all OK!
もはやこれは紛れもない 宇宙で一番のLOVEなんじゃない？
This is already undeniably the greatest LOVE in the universe, right?
答え 待ちきれないんだよ もう
Answer... I just can't wait anymore!
最高速 Fall in Love!
Saikosoku Fall in Love!
いつ 攻撃は最大の防御や
When? Attack is the best defense,
休むヒマもなく 即
Without a moment to rest, immediately...
撃つ！ 撃つ！ 撃つ！ 撃つ！ 六つ！
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot! Shoot! Six!
瞬間で伝えていくんだ
Conveying it in an instant.
大事なのは目と目を合わせることで
The important thing is making eye contact.
愛しても 愛し合ってても 足りない
Even if I love you, even if we love each other, it's not enough.
もっと 本能さらけ出していこう
Let's bare our instincts more!
ねぇ ダーリン 君がいるから最強じゃない？
Hey darling, aren't we the strongest 'cause you're here?
感じ合えるなら最高じゃない？
If we can feel each other, isn't it the best?
ほかに 何もなくたって 大丈夫ですオールOK
Even if we have nothing else, it's fine, all OK!
生まれた場所は問題じゃない この一瞬こそがLOVEなんじゃない？
Where we were born doesn't matter, isn't this very moment LOVE?
ハート まだ...
Heart, still...
ハート まだ 止めないでよ
Don't let my heart stop yet
そう 最高速
Yes, at maximum speed
Ah たとえば世界が止まっても
Ah, even if the world were to stop
胸の高鳴りは止まらない
The throbbing of my heart won't stop
全開でいこう！全開でいこう！全開でいこう！
Go at full throttle! Full throttle! Full throttle!
全開でいこう！全開でいこう！
Full throttle! Full throttle!
ねだり
Coaxing
キミがいるから最強じゃない？
Since you're here, aren't we the strongest?
ずっと一緒なら最高じゃない？
If we're together forever, isn't it the best?
この先 何があったって
No matter what happens from now on
キミとなら All OK!
If it's with you, everything is OK!
もはやこれは紛れもない
This is already unmistakable
宇宙で一番のLOVEなんじゃない？
Isn't it the greatest LOVE in the universe?
答え待ちきれないんだよもう
I can't wait for the answer any longer
最高速
Maximum speed
Fall in Love
生まれた場所は問題じゃない
Where you were born doesn't matter
この一瞬こそがLOVEなんじゃない？
Isn't this very moment LOVE itself?
ハート まだ 止めないでよ
Don't let my heart stop yet
そう 最高速
Yes, at maximum speed
Fall in Love
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
というわけで皆さん、いかがでしたでしょうか？
So, everyone, how was it?
アイドル衣装で踊るの、可愛かったですか？
Was it cute to see me dancing in an idol outfit?
イエーイ、イエーイ！というわけでここからはですね、
Yay, yay! So, from here on,
なんとねねがよくね、配信でもやっているサイン会をですね、
I'm going to hold a signing session, just like I often do in my streams!
行っていきたいと思いまーす！
I'd like to get started!
どうやって今日はやるかっていうと、
As for how we'll do it today...
皆さん、びっくりしたかもしれない、今日は、この画面になんとねねサインしていきたいと思いまーす！
You might be surprised, but today, I'm going to sign directly on this screen!
だれだれ？可愛いかった？あー、すごい、ダンスすごかった！あー、嬉しい！ありがとう！
Who's there? Was it cute? Oh, wow, the dancing was great! Ah, I'm so happy! Thank you!
そしたら、サイン書いておかない？記念すべき1発目！
Well then, shall I write a signature? The memorable first one!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
待って待って、よいしょ！
Wait, wait... Heave-ho!
あ・り・が・と・う
T-H-A-N-K Y-O-U
ね・ね
Ne-ne
あ、ちょっと字汚くなっちゃった、難しい！
Ah, my handwriting got a bit messy. It's hard!
じゃーん！どうどう？凄くない、凄くない？
Ta-da! How is it? Isn't it amazing?
あの、あれにそっくり、プロ、プロ選手みたいなさ、
It looks just like one of those pro athlete's signatures,
めっちゃぽいやん、なんかあれハリウッドっぽい！
it really looks like that. It looks like Hollywood!
うわ、すごいすごい！これ、どんどんやっていきたいと思います！
Wow, amazing, amazing! I want to keep doing more of this!
まだまだ時間がもったいない、全部したいからね！見てこれ、消せるんだよマジでこれ、凄すぎる！
There's still no time to waste, I want to do it all! Look at this, you can actually erase it, this is too incredible!
はぁ、ちょっと息が、息が整わない...
Haa, I can't... I can't catch my breath...
次なんて書いて欲しい？え、次サインにしようかな？
What should I write next? Maybe I'll do another signature?
よ・も・す・ね...
Writing stylized signature...
あ、いいじゃんいいじゃん！はい、じゃーん！
Ah, that's good, that's good! Here, ta-da!
みんな、いっぱいスクショして！うわ、すごいすごい！
Everyone, take lots of screenshots! Wow, amazing, amazing!
あ、そうだ、ねっこ、ねっこ呼ばないと！
Oh, that's right, I have to call the Nekko!
一緒にね、ねっこの皆と一緒にステージでね、盛り上がりたいからちょっと、ねっこ、ねっこおいで！ねっこ、こっちおいで！
Because I want to liven things up on stage with all the Nekko, come here, Nekko! Nekko, come this way!
あ、入場してきている今！あ、来た来た来た！あー、ちょちょちょ、ここにいて、ここに！
Ah, they're entering now! Ah, here they come! Ah, wait wait wait, stay right here!
待って、えーと... 今日は2022年3月14日...
Wait, let's see... Today is March 14, 2022...
あっ！一日間違えちゃった！
Ah! I got the date wrong by a day!
10...待って待って、えーと、13日... ねねアイドル...
10... wait wait, um, the 13th... Nene Idol...
どうどう？ねっこの皆どう？ね、アイドルなってるでしょ、ちゃんと！
How is it? How is it, Nekko? See, I'm a proper idol now!
あ、なってる？本当？はい、一緒に撮るよ！はい、イエーイ、イエーイ！
Ah, I am? Really? Okay, let's take a photo together! Okay, yay, yay!
ということで、ねねの、アイドル衣装見てこれみんな！
And so, everyone, look at Nene's idol outfit!
ちょっと時間もったいないから同時進行で行くさ、これ見て！
Since we don't have much time, I'll do things simultaneously. Look at this!
ねっこの皆とね、アイドルのね、ステージに一緒に立ちたくて、ここにね、描いてもらったの、なんかこれを、これとさ、一緒に、なんかサインでいい感じにさ、あ、ちょっと待ってよ、これを...
I wanted to stand on the idol stage together with all the Nekko, so I had this drawn here. I'll use this and... along with a signature... wait a second, this...
こうして... みんな、大好き！
Like this... I love you all!
なんかみんな、ぬこみたいになっちゃった。好きこれ。
Everyone's turned into nukos. I like this.
好き！イエーイ！
I like it! Yay!
どう、どう？これ。こういう感じ。
How is it? How is it? Like this.
あ、いい、いい、いい、いい。ねえ、どう？すごいいい？
Ah, nice, nice, nice, nice. Hey, how is it? Is it really good?
いいでしょ、いいでしょ。わー！みんな嬉しい。
It's good, right? It's good, right? Wow! Everyone, I'm happy.
本当すごい。この、この技術を使ってくれたスタッフさん本当にありがとう。
It's really amazing. To the staff who used this technology, thank you so much.
めちゃめちゃ感謝してる。なんか無茶言ってごめんなさい。
I'm incredibly grateful. Sorry for making unreasonable requests.
よいしょ。ちょっと大好きとか書きたいな。
Alright. I want to write 'I love you' or something.
え、何がいい？え？ダメ？
Eh, what should I write? Eh? No?
ダメに決まってんだろ。
Of course it's 'no'.
あー、だめだめだめだめだめだめ、だめー！
Ah, no no no no no no, nooo!
ダメだよ。今日からねねもうアイドル衣装着て
You can't. Starting today, Nene's wearing her idol costume
アイドルなんだから。みんな。
and is an idol. Everyone.
あ、いいぞ。こういうの、こういうのだよ。
Ah, this is it. This is the kind of thing.
好き。引き目、引き目でもいけます。こういう感じ。
I like it. Zoom out, it works even from a distance. Like this.
あ、いい！イエーイ！ちゅー。
Ah, nice! Yay! *Kiss*
お迎えしてね。もう一個いけるかな。
Please welcome me. Can I do one more?
何がいい？愛してる、とかいいな。よいしょ。
What would be good? Something like 'I love you' would be nice. Alright.
お答えいたしましょう。よいしょ。
Let me give you an answer. Alright.
ちょっと、慣れてきてねねの字が上手くなってきた。
I'm getting used to it, and Nene's handwriting is getting better.
愛してるぜ！みんな！イエーイ！
I love you guys! Everyone! Yay!
ちょっと待って。どう？いい感じ？
Wait a second. How is it? Looking good?
盛れてる？ねね。あ、いいぞいいぞ。
Do I look cute? Nene. Ah, nice, nice.
ちょっとラストかな。あとどれくらい行けるかな。
Maybe this is the last one. How much longer can I go?
お、まだいけるな。よし。ギリギリまで、ギリギリまで行こうみんな。
Oh, I still have time. Alright. Let's go until the very end, everyone.
消して消して消して。
Erase, erase, erase.
よいしょ。ねっこのみんな、ぬこ、ぬこ、あ、
Alright. All the Nekkos, Nuko, Nuko, ah,
なんかぬこぬこになっちゃった。ぬこぬこになっちゃった。
It kind of turned into 'nuko nuko'. It turned into 'nuko nuko'.
みんなねこみたいになっちゃった。どうしよう。
Everyone turned into cats. What should I do?
ぬこぬこになっちゃった、まいった。
It turned into 'nuko nuko'. I'm stumped.
みんな、ぬこぬこ、みんなね、みんな、ぬこぬこ、イエーイ！
Everyone, nuko nuko, everyone, nuko nuko, yay!
ふー！ぶいぶい！いいじゃん。
Phew! *V-pose* Not bad.
ちょっとこの、字が上手くなったタイミングでサインもう一回書いたりしたいな。
Since my handwriting has improved, I want to try writing my signature again.
頑張りたい。もう一回行きます。
I want to do my best. Here I go again.
あ、いいぞいいぞ。うまいうまいうまい。あ、いいじゃん。
Ah, nice, nice. Good, good, good. Ah, not bad.
ちょっと待って、これ、これでいっぱい撮って、みんな。
Wait a second, take lots of pictures with this, everyone.
いい感じ。じゃーん。
Looking good. Ta-da!
あ、これだったらね、このみんなも見えるね、これで。じゃーん。
Ah, with this, everyone can see you guys too. Ta-da!
ちょっとねこの人も、ねこ、ねこの人も一緒に入ろう。ねこの人、はい。
Let's get the cat people in too. Cat people, here.
ねっこのみんな、イエーイ！
All the Nekkos, yay!
あ、見えなくなっちゃう。こっちのみんな、ちっちゃいみんなが見えなくなっちゃう。
Ah, they're disappearing. The small ones over here are disappearing.
イエーイ！ここに、この指の先に乗って。
Yay! Here, get on the tip of this finger.
あ、いいぞいいぞいいぞいいぞ。いいバランス決めてるね。イエーイ！
Ah, nice, nice, nice, nice. You've got great balance. Yay!
あ、いいじゃん！よしよしよしよし。
Ah, not bad! There, there, there, there.
よし、じゃあちょっとね、次の皆んなにも繋げないといけないから、
Alright, well, I have to pass it on to the next people,
最後に、ちょっと秘密に...
so finally, as a little secret...
これで使って、
Use this,
このまま、このまま進めたいと思います。
and I'll proceed just like this.
というわけで、ねねのパートはもう終わりになっちゃうんですけど、
And so, Nene's part is coming to an end, but...
みんなちょっと見足りないかな？みんな。でもね、
maybe you guys haven't seen enough? But, you know,
アーカイブとかでもいっぱい見てねねの、あのアイドルとしての第一歩、
watch the archive lots of times, and Nene's... that first step as an idol,
みんなで一緒に、進めたら嬉しいと思います。嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if we could take it together. I am happy!
というわけで、次はね、ししろんの枠になりますので、みんなね、
So, next is Shishiron's stream, so everyone...
あ、間違えた！ししろんじゃない！次、ねぽだ！ポルカだ！
Ah, I made a mistake! Not Shishiron! Next is NePo! It's Polka!
次、おまるんの枠なので、
Next is Omarun's stream, so
みんなで一緒におまるんの枠に行きましょう！
let's all go to Omarun's stream together!
というわけで、ねねの枠はここまで！またねね！みんな！バイバーイ！
So, that's it for Nene's stream! See ya-nene! Everyone! Bye-bye!
最後に、バチバチの写真。イエーイ！
Finally, a flashy photo. Yay!
アイドル衣装
Idol costume